<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Posts on :3</title>
    <link>https://bnbdr.github.io/posts/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Posts on :3</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-US</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 09 Sep 2018 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://bnbdr.github.io/posts/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Making Explorer.exe Great Again</title>
      <link>https://bnbdr.github.io/posts/mega/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 09 Sep 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://bnbdr.github.io/posts/mega/</guid>
      <description>The horrid amalgamation of code known as Windows Vista wasn&amp;rsquo;t all bad. As a result of the many effected changes, users were given the ability to run an executable by typing its name in the navigation bar of explorer.exe&amp;rsquo;s window1. By doing so the newly created process had its working directory set to the one shown in that window.
Sadly, even this one redeeming feature has an unfortunate side effect: subsequent attempts to select the path of the directory from the nav bar will yield something else - the absolute path of the executable that was run.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Addictiveness of Typeracer</title>
      <link>https://bnbdr.github.io/posts/typeracer-stats/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 12 Jun 2018 15:14:20 +0300</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://bnbdr.github.io/posts/typeracer-stats/</guid>
      <description>For the uninitiated, typeracer.com is a website that allows you to test your typing speeds against other people using segments of text from different sources.
Judging by the relatively copious number of races I&amp;rsquo;ve partaken in - I probably liked it: Who&amp;rsquo;s my opponent? A big factor in typeracer is your average WPM1. I came to the realization that my most challenging opponent was myself - I had to beat my own average score every race so I won&amp;rsquo;t lower it.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Random XKCD Feed</title>
      <link>https://bnbdr.github.io/posts/xkcd/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 08 Jun 2018 12:38:55 +0300</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://bnbdr.github.io/posts/xkcd/</guid>
      <description>The UI on https://xkcd.com was a tad annoying on mobile so I&amp;rsquo;d written this page that would load random comics as you scroll.
All credit for the original comics goes to Randall Munroe.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Exploiting The Pattern Matching Swiss Knife</title>
      <link>https://bnbdr.github.io/posts/swisscheese/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 06 Jun 2018 15:43:53 +0300</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://bnbdr.github.io/posts/swisscheese/</guid>
      <description>Cheese, Gromit In this short incredibly lengthy post I&amp;rsquo;ll talk about the binary format of YARA rules and also a bit about exploiting two vulnerabilities I found in it.
The two issues were assigned the CVE-IDs CVE-2018-12034 and CVE-2018-12035. They affect YARA 3.7.1 and earlier1.
If you want to skip straight to the exploitation part, go to WAT or take a look at the repo.
I named this SwissCheese becuase I found it amusing that the &amp;ldquo;Pattern Matching Swiss Knife&amp;rdquo; had quite a few holes in it ;D</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>