<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Write Up on bnbdr</title><link>https://bnbdr.github.io/tags/write-up/</link><description>Recent content in Write Up on bnbdr</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-US</language><lastBuildDate>Wed, 22 May 2019 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://bnbdr.github.io/tags/write-up/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>WD My Cloud RCE</title><link>https://bnbdr.github.io/posts/wd/</link><pubDate>Wed, 22 May 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://bnbdr.github.io/posts/wd/</guid><description>In this post I&amp;rsquo;ll explain how I discoverd several vulnerabilities in Western Digital NAS devices1 and used them together to execute code remotely, as root.
To take control of the NAS an attacker needs to be in the same network and know its IP address.
The PoC is available here.
a smelly smell that smells&amp;hellip; smelly It all began after I decided to splurge and purchase the rather techy-oriented NAS option available by WD - the EX2 Ultra.</description></item><item><title>YARA Internals II: Bytecode</title><link>https://bnbdr.github.io/posts/extracheese/</link><pubDate>Tue, 04 Dec 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://bnbdr.github.io/posts/extracheese/</guid><description>Unlike my fastidious explanation of YARA&amp;rsquo;s binary rule format, I&amp;rsquo;ll try to keep this post short by focusing on YARA&amp;rsquo;s VM architecture and how a compiled rule can still be used to run arbitrary code, despite the mitigations added to the latest release of YARA1.
The issues I&amp;rsquo;d discovered were assigned CVE-2018-19974, CVE-2018-19975 and CVE-2018-19976.
To skip straight to the exploitation part jump here, head over to the repo or the GitHub issue.</description></item><item><title>YARA Internals: Compiled Rule Format</title><link>https://bnbdr.github.io/posts/swisscheese/</link><pubDate>Wed, 06 Jun 2018 15:43:53 +0300</pubDate><guid>https://bnbdr.github.io/posts/swisscheese/</guid><description>Cheese, Gromit In this short incredibly lengthy post I&amp;rsquo;ll talk about the binary format of YARA rules and also a bit about exploiting two vulnerabilities I found in it.
The two issues were assigned the CVE-IDs CVE-2018-12034 and CVE-2018-12035. They affect YARA 3.7.1 and earlier1.
If you want to skip straight to the exploitation part, go to WAT or take a look at the repo.
I named this SwissCheese becuase I found it amusing that the &amp;ldquo;Pattern Matching Swiss Knife&amp;rdquo; had quite a few holes in it ;D</description></item></channel></rss>